What exactly happened?
Did you see the killer?
This room
was originally Master Li's bedroom.
Mengzhu switched rooms with Master Li.
So the killer's target
must have been Master Li.
Someone's trying to kill me!
Where are you going?
Come back to the station with me!
Come here!
Help me, Chief Mu!
Someone's trying to kill me!
What?
Someone's trying to kill you?
It's absolutely true!
Mengzhu took the hit for me.
Otherwise,
I would've been the one who died that night!
Oh, my Great Philanthropist Li.
You're the pillar of our Lijia Town!
We're all counting on you.
Don't worry.
We'll send someone to protect you immediately.
Detective Mu is already at the mansion.
With Mu Ying protecting you,
all those monsters and ghosts will have to steer clear.
She alone
is worth the entire Lijia Town police station.
Chief Mu.
Mu Ying can protect me for a while,
but she can't protect me forever.
Then...
Then what do you mean?
Chief Mu,
didn't you want to be promoted to
the Provincial Police Headquarters?
I can put in a word with Marshal Ma
and have him save the chief's position for you.
How about it?
You... You're friends with Marshal Ma?
For Marshal Ma's provincial garrison,
I've provided a lot of military funding.
A mere chief's position
is a piece of cake.
From now on... Good!
What belongs to the Li family
belongs to the Mu family!
Deal!
What?
You want me to marry Philanthropist Li?
Are you crazy?
First thing tomorrow morning,
I'll call the provincial chief
and tell him that Detective Mu
has achieved nothing in Lijia Town
and failed the station's expectations,
and is now requesting to resign as detective.
Just be a good girl and get married,
and live a peaceful life.
Don't...
Don't make the call!
Let me out!
I'm not getting married!
Dad, let me out!
Philanthropist Li
will come pick you up early tomorrow morning for the wedding.
If you marry him,
I guarantee you'll be well provided for.
Keep a close eye on her.
If anything goes wrong, you'll be held responsible!
- Rest assured, Chief. - Let me out!
Even if the Young Miss had extraordinary powers,
she wouldn't be able to escape.
Let me out!
Young Miss,
you'll be a bride tomorrow morning.
Get some rest early.
I don't want to!
Open it!
Let me out!
Master.
The Li Mansion is haunted.
Are we really going in?
We must go in.
The book, Heavenly Craftsmanship,
is our family heirloom.
That day at the Li Mansion,
I saw the box it's kept in.
That proves
that Heavenly Craftsmanship
is inside the Li Mansion.
So,
I have to find it no matter what.
Let's go.
Come on.
The vase has a flowing cloud pattern.
I've seen it in ancient books.
It's unique to the ancient Yuncang Kingdom.
Master.
I need to use the bathroom.
Come with me.
You're such a handful.
Let's go, let's go.
Master.
I'm scared.
Let's go.
Look at you, such a coward.
Useless.
Master.
What is it now?
I think something's following us.
Master, Master!
Master!
Wait for me, Master!
Master.
It's so late, maybe...
Tomorrow morning at seven,
I'll be marrying Mu Ying.
Make sure you get the mansion
decorated properly.
The wedding must be festive.
Get plenty of flowers.
Congratulations, Master.
I'll go prepare right away.
The She-devil is marrying Master Li!
Oh no.
Mu Ying must be in trouble.
Let's go.
I was wondering why, since leaving the Li Mansion this morning,
we hadn't seen her again.
Turns out her dad locked her up.
There are guards inside. What do we do?
Watch this.
Master.
Pingkang Fang. We need a fourth!
Waiting for someone?
Where do you need a fourth?
Pingkang Fang!
What are you waiting for? Hurry up and go!
Thanks, man!
Master.
You sent him away with just one sentence?
Of course.
He was leaning forward,
had dark circles under his eyes,
and even had a die hanging from his waist.
A typical gambler.
The nearest gambling house from here
is at least one li away.
It'll take him a while to get there.
Why is it you two?
You saved me once before,
now I'm returning the favor.
We're even.
What do you mean, even?
Tell me the truth.
Why did you help me?
Isn't it obvious?
My Master likes you!
Shut up!
No, no.
It's not what he said.
Well,
as for why I want to help you solve the case,
I'll find a chance to tell you later.
By the way,
we only have six hours left until dawn.
If you don't want to marry Master Li,
we should work together to solve this quickly.
True.
I worked so hard to become a detective.
Being a detective is so boring.
I think
you'd be better off marrying Master Li.
You'd eat and drink the best every day.
And at night, you'd have ghosts to play with.
How fun! Are you sick in the head?
Why don't you marry him?
I'm looking out for you! Bring up marriage again,
and I'll... In the future,
watch out or I'll beat you up!
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
We have to, before dawn,
which means within six hours,
solve the Li family murders.
I will use my identity as the young mistress of the Li family
as a cover
to gain the Li family's trust
and get more clues.
Coming, coming!
Madam.
Where is Philanthropist Li?
Master Li went back to his room.
Aren't you two getting married tomorrow morning?
You're just in time, Madam.
I'm preparing your wedding dress.
I know about the wedding.
That's exactly why I'm here.
Within four months,
four women died in the Li Mansion.
All causes of death were accidental.
We now know
the method used to kill Mengzhu.
But...
the hidden weapons and needles on the puppet,
as well as the murder weapon,
we haven't found any of them.
And we have no clue about the killer.
The Li Mansion is so big,
where are we supposed to look?
Madam.
This wedding dress was left by First Wife.
You two are about the same size.
Try it on first to see if it fits.
First Wife?
Do you remember
how First Wife died?
First Wife...
her soul was taken by the Flower Demon.
The Flower Demon?
That's right.
It was the Flower Demon.
After First Wife died,
she turned into the Flower Demon.
Whenever night falls,
she returns to the Li Mansion.
First Wife!
First Wife is back!